imgshots.com 2010-04-28

# Privacy Policy | FDC: Freedom Dignity Control

### Freedom Dignity Control – Website Privacy Policy

The following policy dictates the manner in which Freedom Dignity Control collects and uses information gathered from users of this website.

#### Privacy

Our users’ privacy is extremely important to us and we are committed to safeguarding the information you entrust to us. Freedom Dignity Control will not share the information you provide us with any third party without your express permission -- unless the release of said information is required by government subpoena.

#### Information Collection Practices

Freedom Dignity Control may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. We may also collect information about how Users interact with our website . This information is obtained through analysis of server logs and through the use of “cookies” placed on user machines. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on a PC to identify the User should they visit the website again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our website.

#### Information Usage

Freedom Dignity Control may use personally identifiable information collected through our website to contact Users regarding products and services offered by Freedom Dignity Control. We may also use information collected through our website for research regarding the effectiveness of the website and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of Freedom Dignity Control.

#### No Contact/ No Usage

Unless you specifically opt in, no information about you will be used or stored for any research. Neither will you be contacted by Freedom Dignity Control.

#### Information Disclosure

Freedom Dignity Control will not disclose information about customers or users without express permission unless the release of said information is required by government subpoena. However, we may transfer information collected from Users in connection with a sale of our business.
